我哥哥在哪
Where's my brother?!
(走过的路)
你是什么
What are you?
我是恶魔
I'm a demon.
大家一起唱
Everybody!
你欠我的
You...owe me.
那我们达成协议了吗
So, do we have a deal?
你杀了我爸爸
You killed my dad.
母亲
Mother.
我会出去的
I'll get out.
把那姑娘给我
Give me the girl.
告诉我你是没别的办法
Tell me you had to do this.
(如今)
儿子  儿子
Son? Son?
费格斯
Fergus!
你怎么了
What's the matter?
-没什么  -没什么
- Nothing. - Nothing?
你吓得一身汗
You're soaked in the horror sweat.
上次见到你这样还是黑死病的时候
Haven't seen that since the plague years.
亲爱的  要我做什么吗
Darlin', what can I do?
不用了  你个臭婊子
Not a thing, you evil bitch.
"不用了  你个臭婊子"  母亲
"Not a thing, you evil bitch," Mother.
你先别那么热乎
Let's not get too cozy just yet.
[邪恶力量 第10季第10集]
她几乎不跟我说话
She barely speaks to me.
只是像只受伤的野兽那样看着我
She's like a wounded animal, just watching me.
小卡  告诉你
Look, Cass, you know what?
你那晚真的是在尽力做正确的事了
You really tried to do the right thing that night. You did.
跟克莱尔在一起的那个人  兰迪
This guy Claire was hanging out with, uh, Randy...
他一直在利用她
All he did was use her.
她以为他是好人
Yeah, well, she thought he was kind,
而且为此爱他
and for that she loved him.
这足以说明她实在不经常遇到好人
Shows how little kindness there was in her life.
不管兰迪做了什么  他都不该被...
You know, whatever Randy did, he didn't deserve...
是啊  我知道
No, yeah. I know. I know.
没错
I hear you.
迪恩以前也曾被迫杀人  我们都经历过
Dean has had to kill before. We... we both have.
但...那...
But...that was...
怎么了
That was what?
-迪恩  -是屠杀
- Dean. - It was a massacre.
就是这样
That's what it was.
我曾经是个猎人
I mean, there was a time I was a hunter,
而不是个冷血杀人狂
not a stone-cold killer?
说吧
You can say it.
你没说错
You're not wrong.
我越界了
I crossed the line.
这东西必须得去掉
Guys, this thing's got to go.
-没那么容易  -那就把它烧掉
- That won't be easy. - Well, then, burn it off!
-割下来  -那不光是皮肉上的东西
- Cut it off! - It is more than just a physical thing.
要去除其效力需要很强大的力量
It will take a very powerful force to remove the effect.
迪恩  我们翻查过了所有的传说
Dean, we have been through all the lore.
什么都没有
There's nothing.
这一直能追溯到创世纪的时候
This reaches back to the time of creation.
可能远在有传说之前
It may predate the lore.
如果我们有恶魔石碑或许还有希望
If we had the Demon Tablet, maybe.
你说石碑丢了
But you said it was missing.
是啊
It is.
或许还有一个办法
There may be another way.
有什么事吗
Oh, may I, uh, help you?
陛下不希望您没人陪同  一个人乱走
His majesty didn't want you wandering around unattended.
尤其是在这里
Certainly not in here.
我就是想找点食物
Oh, no, I was just looking for a wee scrap of food.
他们给我拿的东西  怎么能入国王之母的金口
That swill they bring me... hardly fit for the mother of the King.
这我就无从知道了
I wouldn't know.
我又不吃东西
I don't eat.
劳烦您  我得遵守命令
If you please, I have my orders.
可怜人
Oh, you poor, dear man.
是叫格思里吧
Guthrie, is it?
你生怕惹他不高兴  是吧
Terrified of displeasing him, aren't you?
我了解我儿子的德行
I know how my son can be.
你们都怕得要死
You're all scared spitless.
但孩子总归是听娘的
Still, a boy listens to his mum.
我很乐意替你说句好话
I'd be happy to put in a good word for you.
不必了  多谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
格思里
Guthrie...
不管这是什么  无聊死我了
Whatever this is, it bores me rigid.
我要不要签字啊
Do I sign or not?
我认为没问题  陛下
I found it in order, Sir.
签吧
Do sign.
妈妈
Mummy.
无聊吗  想自杀吗  两样都有吗
Bored? Suicidal? Both?
没有  亲爱的
Hardly, my dear.
我学到了好多
I'm learning so much.
你这破地方
This place of yours...
我算是明白你为什么是这副样子了
poor thing, I see now why you are the way you are.
天呐
My goodness!
他们的不满  闲言碎语  密谋
The discontent, the gossip, the plotting.
-密谋  -是啊
- Plotting? - Aye.
那个...是最糟糕的
And that one... worst of the lot.
你一定提放他  记住我的话
Watch yourself around him, mark my word.
要知道下面地牢里那个守卫
You do realize that's exactly what you said
杰拉德  你当初也是这么说他的
about the guard, Gerald, down in the cells.
我说错了吗
And was I not right?
我知道你不信任我  这我活该
I know, I know you mistrust me, and I earned that.
这真是可惜  我远比你其他的臣民
And it's a pity because more than any of your other subjects,
更希望你顺顺利利
I wish you success.
我知道你打的什么主意  母亲
I know what you're up to here, Mother.
是吗  亲爱的
Do you, dear?
你是在无耻地巴结我  以期我放了你
You are shamelessly sucking up so that I'll free you
你好再次去胡作非为  给我捣乱
so you can run amok and gum up my operation once again.
-不必了  -别傻了
- No, thank you. - Free, schmee.
我在这儿能跟儿子待在一起  还要什么自由啊
Why would I want to be free when I can be here with my son?
难道你是国王
Does it hurt that you are the king
这对我有利是件坏事吗
and there are advantages for me in that?
不是
No.
更重要的是  我是个母亲
But more important, I'm a mother.
我就是骄傲  你还要告我吗
Sue me... I'm proud.
抱歉了  我就不蜷在你怀里了
Excuse me if I don't curl up in your lap.
你可抛弃了我三百年
You did manage to stay away for 300 years.
够了  这我们都说过了
Please. We've been over this.
当地人当时打算以巫术罪审判我
The locals were going to try me for witchcraft,
这绝没有好事  我必须逃跑
and that never ends well. I had to flee!
-你本可来把我接走  -我随后得到了
- You could have sent for me! - Well, then came the chance
跟随伟大的米兰女巫  利蒂系娅·迪·奥比欧尼
to study under the great Milanese witch,
学习的宝贵机会
Letitia Di Albioni.
然后我又跟大巫师团闹僵了
And then there was the unpleasantness with the Grand Coven.
总之  那种环境根本不适合带孩子
Anyway, it was no environment for a child!
那你就把我锁在一个破济贫院里吗
So locking me away in a squalid workhouse was your solution?!
我不会为做一个职业女性而道歉
I will not apologize for being a career woman.
再说
Besides...
对我们这样的人来说  三百年算什么
What's 300 years more or less to folks like us?
不足挂齿
Nothing.
我这不回来了
I'm back now.
我们可以做一家人
We can be a family.
他们应该到了
They should be here by now.
有消息说他们要迟到吗
Was there word of a delay?
我只是个看门的
All I do is watch the door.
你在等谁  卡西迪奥
Who are you expecting, Castiel?
谢谢  英格丽德
Thank you, Ingrid.
我照你说的做了  这很冒险  卡西迪奥
I did as you asked... at great risk, Castiel.
我知道
I know.
我找你是因为我知道你跟我一样
I approached you because I know you share my belief
相信保护人类是天使的职责
that it is Angels' mission to protect humans.
而我或许能消除一个对人类很严重的威胁
And it's possible I can eliminate a great threat to them,
但我需要他帮忙
but...I will need his help.
一定要把他分毫不伤地送回来
He must be returned... intact.
明白了吗
Is that clear?
是的
Yes.
我上次见你时就说过  我能逃出监狱
Told you last time I saw you I'd get out of the slammer.
相信我  这只是暂时的
It's temporary. Trust me.
说到暂时
Well, speaking of temporary,
你又借到了别的能量吧
you must have borrowed some more Grace...
你气色很棒
you're looking very good.
不过我们都知道这撑不了多久
Of course, we both know that won't last.
你是为这个吗  你觉得我会帮你
Is that why I'm here? You think I'm gonna help you?
这不是为了我
This isn't about me.
当然了
Of course not.
伟大的卡西迪奥绝不会如此
The great Castiel never stoops to such...
自私
selfishness.
那到底是为了什么
So, what is it, then?
我懂了
Oh, I see.
你一定没跟英格丽德提过他吧
I'm betting you didn't tell Ingrid about him.
你好啊  萨姆
Hello, Sam.
来杀我的吗
Here to kill me?
好漂亮的房间
Lovely room.
你就把那些重口的小妞都带到这儿来  对吗
It's where you bring the kinky chicks. Am I right?
我来提问
I'll ask the questions here.
你呢  你唯一的任务
You... your only job
就是提供信息
is to provide information.
好吧
Oh, well.
信息的确是我的专长
Information does happen to be a specialty.
我脑子里存着二十多亿的知识呢
Got about 2 Billion fun facts up here.
当然  我愿不愿说
Of course, whether I choose to cough one up or not
就是另一回事了
is another matter.
我们想知道如何除掉迪恩手臂上的该隐血印
We need to know how to remove the Mark of Cain from Dean's arm.
什么
What?
他复活了
He's back?
因为血印吗
Because of the Mark?
那么
So...
他成恶魔了
He's a demon.
不是
No.
那是怎么回事
Okay, what then?
怎么  他"杀人"了吗
What, did he "kill a human" or something?
他爆发了
He's gone nuclear!
口吐白沫
Total foaming-at-the-mouth,
彻底发疯了
balls-out maniac.
简直太棒了
That's fantastic!
你知道怎么去除血印吗
Do you know how to remove it?
或许吧
Maybe.
但问题是
But here's the thing...
你如果指望我帮忙
you expect any help out of me,
就把你的疯子哥哥看住了
you keep that crazy brother of yours on a short leash.
伙计
Buddy...
我根本不在乎你会怎么样
I don't care what happens to you.
你杀了我哥哥
You killed my brother.
(阿斯托里亚旅馆)
我本想在你回来之前就走掉的
I was hoping to be gone by the time you got back.
如果你不喜欢这间房  我们可以换一个
If you don't like the room, we can find another one.
不是房间的问题  卡西迪奥
It's not the room, Castiel.
是你
It's you.
这是行不通的
This isn't going to work.
拜托
I mean, come on.
你长得像我父亲
You look like my father.
这是他的身体  但他已经死了
It is his body, but he's dead.
我明白  你觉得愧疚  但你...
And I get it, you feel bad, but you...
不管你是谁  你对我毫无意义
whoever you are... are nothing to me.
克莱尔  不是这样的
Claire, that's not true.
我对你如今的生活
I'm in large part responsible
负有很大责任
for the way your life has unfolded.
我有帮助你的义务
I-I have a responsibility to help you.
不  你没有
No. You don't.
克莱尔
Claire.
你见识过可怕的事
You have seen things,
你经历了一些你这年纪的孩子不该经历过的事
you've been through things that no one your age should have.
你迷失方向了
And you are adrift.
我想帮你建立新生活
I want to... I want to help you have a life.
我有生活
I have a life.
我活得挺好
I'm good with it.
如果你是指正常的生活
If what you mean is a normal life,
那是不可能了
well, that ship has sailed.
不非得如此  你还年轻
Well, that doesn't have to be the case. You're still young.
别再拿父亲的口气跟我说话了
Stop talking to me like you're my father.
你杀了我父亲
You killed my father.
你那个朋友
And that friend of yours
杀了我唯一接近亲人的人
killed the last thing I had closest to family.
你是说兰迪吗
Are you speaking of Randy?
亲人
Family?
那男人想要强暴你
A man had you in that room,
兰迪却毫无作为
and Randy didn't make a move to help you.
或许是因为有人拿枪指着他
Maybe because he was at gunpoint.
迪恩·温彻斯特是个禽兽
Dean Winchester's a monster.
或许我们每个人都有兽性的一面
It's possible there's a little monster in all of us.
你想要我相信你
You want me to trust you?
你居然还这么维护他
And the fact that you'd even try to defend him
就足以说明我不能信任你
just proves to me that I can't.
-克莱尔  -不  卡西迪奥
- Claire. - No, Castiel!
我受够了
I'm done.
我得自己去闯荡
I have to be on my own.
生活多讨厌啊
Ain't life a bitch?
我这种不受重视的人
Nebbishy little guy, me,
总是跟有勇无谋的猛汉作对
always sticking it to the lunkhead jocks.
别管什么血印了  我们杀了他吧
You know what? Screw the Mark. Let's just kill him.
他真是病得不轻
Boy, he really is a mess.
谁能想到血印会这么厉害
Who knew the Mark was so toxic?
其实
Well...
我是知道的
Actually, I did.
你知道血印迟早会控制你
You know it is going to own you sooner than later.
嗯  我们要怎么除掉它
Yeah, so do how do we get rid of it?
就这样啊  这就客套完了
What, just like that, social hour's over?
没错
Yes.
现在有请主讲人
And now we're moving on to our keynote speaker.
就是你
Which is you...
我们来问问题
With us asking the questions
我呢  则会有幸
and me taking the personal pleasure
亲自把回答从你这里割出来
of carving the answers out of you.
喂  等等啊  汉子
Just... whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on there, badass.
别这么阴郁
Lighten up.
你为什么就直接认定我不会帮忙啊
Why do you just assume I'm not gonna be helpful?
因为你是个混蛋
Because you're a dickwad.
但我是你们的混蛋啊
But I'm your dickwad.
我的..."心里"
I have a special place in my...
可是揣着你俩的
non-heart for you both,
所以呢
to which end... ta-da!...
我很乐意帮你去掉这个圣经版的青春痘
I would be tickled to help you pop this biblical zit.
但想要做到  你会需要一样东西
To do it, you are gonna need one specific thing.
你的老伙计
Your old bud...
第一刃
The First Blade.
什么
What?
我说了
As I said...
生活最讨厌了
Ain't life a bitch?
这绝对是我听过的最差的主意了
This is the single worst idea I've ever heard.
你刚刚杀了一屋子人
You just whacked a whole houseful of people
这还是在第一刃不在身边的时候呢
and that's when the Blade was nowhere around,
现在你又想直接接触第一刃了吗
and now you want to be in actual contact with it?
我们并不知道我要接触到第一刃
We don't know that I have to be in contact with it.
我们只知道我们需要第一刃
All we know is that we need it.
不不  我们只知道他是这么说
No, no, no. All we know is, he says we need it.
我们都不知道他想让我们拿它做什么
We don't even know what he wants us to do with it.
一步步来  我们小心行事
Okay, step a time, all right? We play it safe,
我们搞明白用到的咒语  其原理
we learn whatever this spell is, how it works,
不让我真正碰到第一刃
and we keep the Blade out of my hand.
等等  你确定不是血印
Wait a second. Are you sure this isn't the Mark
让你想拿到那东西吗
making you want the damn thing?
我们为什么要相信梅塔特隆的任何话啊
I mean, why would we trust anything Metatron says?
我不信任梅塔特隆
I don't trust Metatron.
你不...那怎么办
You don't tr-- then what?
如果他是在撒谎  那他是想怎么样
What's his game if he is lying, okay?
没有我  第一刃毫无用处
W-- the Blade without me is useless,
我拿着第一刃  只会对他不利
the Blade with me is trouble for him.
那他想怎么样
Then what does he want?
我不知道  但如果我们不试试
I don't know, but if we weren't willing to take a shot,
那又何必带他来
then what was the point in bringing him here?
除非你有更好的主意
Unless you got a better idea.
你还记得你每晚喂过羊之后
Of course you recall the lovely lullaby I sang to you nightly
我给你唱的摇篮曲吧
after you fed the goat.
你从没给我唱过摇篮曲
You never sung me a lullaby.
你喂我威士忌  直到我昏睡过去
You dosed me with whiskey until I passed out.
我当时就挺擅长用药的
Even then, I had a touch for pharmacology.
你妈妈是个天才
Your mum was a prodigy.
有意思
Funny.
我可不会这么形容你
Not what I called you.
公事
Business.
松鼠  好久不见
Squirrel. It's been a while.
又回到从前的样子了吗
Back to your former self?
克劳力  我们要尽快见个面
Crowley, we need to meet A.S.A.P.
在哪
Where?
得走了
Got to go.
急事  国家大事
Urgent. A matter of state.
我的儿子
My son.
好个大人物
So important.
要等你吃晚餐吗
Shall I wait dinner for you?
你不做饭  我不吃饭
You don't cook. I don't eat.
这样多棒
It's a perfect arrangement.
连句再见都不说
Not even a goodbye.
我妈妈发疯离家之后
After my mom split and went crazy,
兰迪对我视如己出
Randy was like a father to me.
我先失去了第一个父亲  又失去了第二个
First I lose my first dad, then I lose my second,
是谁杀了他  毁了我的生活呢
and who killed him and trashed my life?
杀了我第一个父亲  还想做我第三个父亲的
The buddy of the guy who killed my first dad
人的好兄弟
and wants to be my third dad.
听上去跟我的经历很像呢
Wow. Sounds just like my life.
麻烦和痛苦  家庭只会带给你这个
Complications and pain... that's all family gets you.
是啊
Yes.
所以我和托尼总是到处走  不留牵挂
That's why me and Tony keep moving... no strings.
你跟我们待一阵吧
Hey, why don't you hang with us for awhile
把这堆麻烦甩在身后
and unload this whole mess?
你还是好好考虑一下吧
Um, you might want to reconsider.
我身边的人经常很快就遭遇噩运
People near me get pretty unlucky pretty fast.
又是他
That's him again.
杀了你第二个爸爸
The guy who killed your second dad,
还是杀了你第一个爸爸的人
or the guy who killed your first dad?
后面那个
The second thing.
-叫他滚蛋  -我说了
- Tell him to get lost. - I did.
他是个..
He's a...
挨了打还把另一边脸凑过去的那种人
"turn the other cheek" kind of guy.
亲
Hon...
你看上去是个好人
You seem real sweet,
但好心收拾不了麻烦
but sweetness don't clean up messes.
是啊
Right.
不是吧  克劳力  不说话啊
Really, Crowley? Radio silence?
说点什么吧
Look, say something.
你们要我做什么
You want me to do what?!
我们需要你把...
Okay, look, we need you to bring back...
把第一刃拿回来  休想
Bring back the Blade? I don't think so!
你不用把那东西给我
You don't have to give the thing to me.
-当然  -不
- I should say not. - No, no.
你去给拿回来  放在你手里  直到我们需要用
Just retrieve it and hang onto it until we need it.
你  小鹿  你是精神正常的那个
You. Moose. You're the sane one.
你也同意吗
You on board with this?!
蒂塔妮亚之翼
Wings of Titania,
让我开启天眼
bear mine eyes aloft as I bid thee...
真是疯了
It's insane.
你要我为迪恩·温彻斯特取回这世上
You want me to procure the most dangerous weapon on the planet
最危险的武器
for Dean Winchester,
而他每次碰到这武器都会发疯
the man who goes mental every time he touches it!
我以为你是叫我上来喝酒  看个电影呢
I thought you wanted to go for a beer, catch a film.
这计划如果能成功
Look, if this plan works...
这不是计划  这很可能是给我们族类
It's not a plan. It's a probable death sentence
判下死刑
for me and my kind.
如果成功  对你有好处
If it works, it's better for you.
等血印去除了  第一刃就失效了
Look, when the Mark is gone, the Blade can't operate.
双赢  是吧
Win-win. Huh? Win-win!
你够了
Stop that.
它藏好了就没法用了
It can't operate. It's hidden.
第一刃虽然暂停使用了  但血印还很活跃
Okay, look, the Blade might be powered down, but the Mark is not,
我在尽力控制自己了
and I'm doing everything I can to keep it together.
你觉得我现在杀的人算多了吗
Now, you think the body count around me is high right now?
等血印完全控制了我再看吧
Wait till Hal takes over.
我们猜你一定把第一刃藏在了很远的地方
We figured you stashed the Blade somewhere far away...
当然  跟我的骨头一起  埋在一个地下室里
Damn right. It's in a crypt with my bones.
那怎么样
All right, well?
我讨厌这时候的关岛
I hate Guam this time of year.
为什么陛下要通过你传信
And why is this imperial communiqué coming through you?
国王有事向来对我当面交待
The King always deals with me mano a mano.
国王  我儿子  有更要紧的事要做
Well, the king, my son, had pressing affairs
便让我  他母亲  来找你
and asked me, his mother, to speak with you,
他最信任的...下属
his most trusted... Underling.
他说  "我只能信任格思里来办这件事"
He said, "Only Guthrie can be trusted with this task."
这不好吧
I don't know.
你不用知道什么  只要听命令就行
It's not your place to know, just to obey.
我说过  作为陛下的母亲
I did mention that as his majesty's mother,
我最清楚什么或者谁对我儿子最好
I have an unerring sense of what or who is best for my son, yes?
真令人反胃
Ad nauseam.
你该记得  是我揭露了叛徒杰拉德
You will recall it was I who exposed the traitor Gerald.
就是被国王处死的那个
The one the King executed.
不是所有恶魔都那么好
Turns out not all demons are nice.
事关我家儿子  我可很凶悍
And I am a tigress when it comes to my bonny lad.
国王要我做什么事
What is this task the King requires?
从你的简历来看  你升职之前
Your résumé indicates you were a crossroads demon
曾是个十字路口恶魔
before your promotion?
是的
I was.
那你一定常出行
Then you do travel.
是不是
Is that not correct?
又要拿出第一刃
The first Blade is back in play,
而且还是克劳力去取吗
and Crowley is the one getting it?
我不想危言耸听  但是...
I don't mean to be an alarmist, but you...
你了解我们的
Yeah, well, you know us.
我们坑自己就要坑到底
When we screw ourselves, we like to go whole hog.
这可是让第一刃
This would be the Crowley
把迪恩变成恶魔的克劳力啊
who let the Blade turn Dean into a demon?
我没得选
I don't have a choice, okay?
我不这么做  我就没救了
I don't do this, I'm down the rabbit hole.
神智被侵蚀  然后就会变成杀人魔
Hear evil, see evil, do evil... the trifecta.
小卡  让我们操心这事吧
Cass, look, let us worry about this.
你光应付克莱尔就够忙了
You've got enough on your plate with Claire.
克莱尔走了
Claire is gone.
去哪了
Gone where?
不知道
I don't know.
我本该拦下她的
I-I-I should have stopped her,
但我确定她肯定又要
but I am certain that she is destined
遇上麻烦和失望了
for more trouble and disappointment.
她充满了...愤怒
She is so... so full of rage.
伙计  如果我能弥补  我会的
Listen, man, if I could make it better, I would.
我就是为了这个而来
That's actually why I'm here.
我希望你能去找她
I was hoping you might reach out to her.
-我吗  -是的
- Me? - Yes.
你开玩笑吧  我大概是她最不想
Seriously, I'm probably the last person
见到的人了
she would want to hear from.
我觉得你们或许会有共同语言...
I thought there would be a connection --
你俩都是乱套到极点的人
one extremely messed-up human to another.
你可以解释一下你为何杀了她唯一的朋友
You could explain why you murdered her only friend.
好吧  要这么说的话
Oh, well, yeah, when you put it like that.
我只知道...她是不会和我说话的
All I know... is she won't talk to me.
我以为如果她看清了兰迪是个怎样的人
I thought if she understood the kind of man Randy was
自己本来有多危险
and the danger she was in,
她也许就会...
she might...
管他呢  为什么不呢
What the hell? Why not?
反正我们似乎都在赌博
Long shots seem to be the theme around here.
我要去做个三明治
I'm gonna go make a sandwich.
我会把她的号码短信给你
Holler. I'll text you her number.
好吧
Okay.
我喜欢发短信
I like texting.
符号表情什么的
Emoticons.
他看起来很平静啊...
He seems calm...
考虑到血印的影响
Considering the effects of the Mark
以及梅塔特隆就在身边
and Metatron in proximity.
是过于平静了
Too calm.
我想他是担心假如自己爆发了会发生什么
I think he is worry about what will happen if he pops a cork.
(麦克劳德)
我坐骨神经痛
Sciatica.
我需要一张硬一点的椅子
Oh, I need a firm chair.
是嘛
So I see.
我拿到了
I have it.
这是我的职责
This is my responsibility.
我只会将它交给国王
I will deliver it only to the King.
你展现出了无懈可击的忠诚  格思里
You have demonstrated unimpeachable loyalty, Guthrie.
你比其他任何人都更配享有
You more than any deserve this reward
君主感激的报答
from a grateful monarch.
别惹我  马屁精
Don't screw with me, sycophant.
这怎么回事
What in hell?!
是啊  这地狱里到底是怎么了啊
Exactly! What the hell is going on in hell?!
你说过格思里是你最好最信任的手下
You said Guthrie was one of your best, your most trusted,
但我却发现他在群臣之中挑拨离间
and -- and yet I found him inciting unrest amongst the court.
-不可能  -是吗
- Can't be true. - Can't it?
他说你和某个叫温彻斯特的人勾结在一起
He -- he said you were colluding with someone called Winchester?
是不是
Y-yes?
还说你要去帮他拿...
And that you were going to fetch him --
拿什么来着
oh, oh, what was it?
第一刃  那东西能把我们全杀了
The First Blade, which could kill us all.
他说他先一步拿到了刀  因为你不可信
He said he got it first because you can't be trusted.
不用说  我和他当面对质
Naturally, I confronted him,
然后他袭击了我
and he attacked me.
我别无选择
I had no choice.
我之前看到过格里思攻击我的幻视
I had a vision of Guthrie attacking me.
预兆
A prophecy.
我最会解读预兆了
I am an interpreter of signs.
-这不可能  -我知道  宝宝
- It's not possible. - I know, Sonny.
但是...
And yet --
他怎么可能知道
How could he have known?
到处都有探子
Spies everywhere.
我警告过你
I did try to warn you.
费格斯  他提到的什么温彻斯特
Fergus, these Winchesters he mentioned,
不是指猎人温彻斯特吧
they're not the hunter Winchesters, are they?
因为他们对我们也是极大的威胁
Because they, too, can be a great danger for us.
今天是我们运气好
I mean, today we got lucky,
但谁知道明天又会如何呢
but tomorrow, who knows?
你还剩谁可以信任
Who is there left for you to trust?
我们爱死住在那里了
Oh, we loved living there.
那是我们的梦之屋
It was our dream house.
不过  那家人度假回来了
Of course, the family came home from vacation,
把一切都搅黄了
screwed up everything.
我差点尿了
I just about peed myself
那家妻子从包里掏出了枪
when the wife pulled that gun out of her purse.
我们狂奔而出  跑了两里地
We tore out there, ran two miles,
光着屁股
bare-ass naked.
我是迪恩
Hey, it's Dean.
听着  克莱尔  我们得当面谈谈
Look, Claire, we need to talk in person.
你定个地点  好吗
Just tell me where, okay?
-打给我  -又是那个人吗
- Call me. - That him again?
那个给你造成那么多伤痛的人
Guy that caused you so much grief?
更糟
Worse.
迪恩·温彻斯特  那个屠杀了兰迪的人
Dean Winchester -- the one who butchered Randy.
为什么
And why?
这个迪恩和兰迪有什么关系
What was this Dean's connection to Randy?
他都不认识兰迪  也不认识其他人
He didn't even know him. Or the others.
但他却把他开膛破肚了
And he gutted him,
我看见他站在那里  浑身是血
and I saw him standing there, soaked in blood,
看起来很享受
looking like he enjoyed it.
如今他想见我  和我谈话
And now he wants to meet and talk.
也许你应该见他
Maybe you should.
什么
What?
我和托尼都很担心你
Me and Tony are worried for you.
有这个人在身边
With this guy around,
你就得一直提心吊胆提防着
you're always gonna be looking over your shoulder.
我们之前处理过这类情况
We've handled situations like this before.
我们可以解决他
We can take care of him
这样他们就不会再来烦你了
so that they won't bother you anymore.
把他狠狠揍一顿
Beat him up bad.
或者...
Or...
一劳永逸地解决他...
something more permanent..
喂
Yeah.
松鼠
Squirrel.
我拿到了
I've got it.
很好
That's good to hear.
当然了  我会留着它
Of course, I'm gonna hang onto it
直到你查明把那玩意从手臂上去掉的办法
until you work out how to get that thing off your arm.
我猜你不是来叙旧的
I'm guessing you're not here to reminisce.
不  我们按你说的做了  我们拿到了第一刃
No, we did what you said. We have the First blade.
不在这里
Not here?
不在你这里
Not on your person?
我没说
Not saying.
所以该你说了  接下来呢
So, back to you. What's next?
接下来就有趣了
This is where it gets kind of interesting.
这里非常寂寞
It's very lonely here,
除了思考没别的事可做
and I have little to do but think.
我就想到
And it occurred to me
你真的很需要把血印弄掉
that you really need this Mark taken off of you.
为了那么做
And in order to do that,
你真的很需要我
you really need me.
所以  我们这么做
So, here's the deal --
我告诉你的第一个步骤
that first little tip I gave you --
是免费的
a freebie,
因为你是你
just 'cause you're you.
之后的每一步
Every future step?
你都要付出代价
They're gonna cost you.
很大的代价
Big.
提醒你一下  有一长串呢
Oh, and FYI -- there's a bunch.
你要干什么  猛男
Whatcha doing there, Slugger?
我要清算一笔很久都没清算的仇
I'm settling a score that's taken way too long to settle.
与此同时  我要得到一些信息
Oh, and while I do that, I'm gonna get some information...
我会享受这过程里的每一分钟
...and I'm gonna enjoy every minute of it
因为你要把一切都告诉我  一切
because you're gonna tell me everything -- all of it --
我不会为此付出一丁点代价
and it ain't gonna cost me a damn dime...
猛男
Slugger.
好吧  在我动手前
All right, I'm gonna ask this exactly once
我再问一次
before it gets ugly --
去除血印的下一步要做什么
What is the next step in removing the Mark?
我再重复一遍  每一步你都得付出代价
I repeat my offer -- each step costs you.
你糊涂了
You're confused.
你看  你不告诉我的每一步
See, each step you don't give me...
都会让你付出代价
is gonna cost you.
我早该收拾你了
And it's been a long time coming.
从何说起呢
I mean, where do I begin?
偷走小卡的能量
Stealing Cass' Grace...
驱逐天使
Casting out the Angels...
让嘉德利尔借我弟弟之手杀死凯文
Making Gadreel kill Kevin using my brother's hands,
挑起天使战争
starting an Angel war...
还有...对了
And, oh, yeah...
你杀了我
...you killed me.
迪恩·温彻斯特居然来批判我的道德品行
My morality is being judged by Dean Winchester?
有多少人因为相信你
How many people have suffered and died
而承受痛苦  死去
because they believed in you?
你多少次骗了萨姆
How many times have you lied to Sam,
包括  对了
including, oh, by the way,
他被天使附身的时候
when he was possessed by an Angel?
你说"这都是为了大局"
And you say, "Oh, well, it's all for the greater good,"
但是最近  兄弟
but lately, buddy,
大局什么的  就不重要了  是不是
that greater-good thing just went away, didn't it?
现在  你想杀人就杀人
Now people die just because you want them to!
很好  迪恩
Good, Dean.
再狠一些
Go darker.
再堕落些
Go deeper!
你肯定发现血印让你变得暴躁时
Surely you've noticed every time you respond,
你都会有所回应
when the Mark gets you all twitchy,
它对你的控制越来越深
you fall deeper under its spell.
你觉得殴打几个人类和恶魔会让情况更糟吗
You think roughing up a few humans and demons makes it worse?
打上帝的书记员试试吧  恶霸
Try messing with the scribe of God, bucko!
很晚了
It's late.
我开车去四处转转  看能不能找到克莱尔
I'm gonna drive around a little bit, see if I can find Claire.
现在吗
Right now?
我得试试
I have to try.
好吧  小心点
All right, well, be careful.
小卡
Hey, Cass?
迪恩在哪
Where's Dean?
凯文的死呢
And Kevin's death?
都怪你
All on you.
是你让他一直身陷险境
You put him in harm's way and kept him there.
嘉德利尔附身在萨姆身上
Gadreel possessing Sam?
是谁骗萨姆让他附身的
Who was it who tricked Sam into letting him in?
还有我的个人最爱
Oh, and then my personal favorite --
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester,
整个人生
whose entire existence
都在与黑暗和鬼怪做斗争
is defined by a war on the dark and monstrous,
居然跟地狱之王全国到处秀恩爱
bromancing his way around the country with the King of Hell!
我们再试一次
Let's try this again.
下一步是什么
What is... the next step?
你们人类那种粗鲁的说法
What is it you humans say so...
是什么来着
inelegantly?
对了
Oh, yes.
去死吧
Go screw yourself.
迪恩
Dean!
该下重手了
Now it's time to get serious.
迪恩
Dean!
把血印从我胳膊上移除的下一步是什么
What is the next step in removing this Mark from my arm?
迪恩  开门
Dean, open the door.
开门
Hey! Open the door!
下一步是什么
What is the next step?!
让开
Move!
瞧啊
Behold...
河流将终结于源头
The river shall end at the source.
不  迪恩
No! Dean!
住手  住手
Hey! Stop! Stop!
你要杀死他了
You were killing him!
我得把他带回去
I have to take him back.
-小卡  不会再发生这种事了  -我保证过
- Cass, this won't happen again. - I gave my word.
我在天堂还有关系要修复
I have fences to mend in heaven,
这下  我要做很多解释了
and as it is, I have a lot to explain.
如果你再叫我帮忙
If you ever ask me for help again,
我宁愿死
I will choose death.
你明白这会越来越糟吧  迪恩
You realize it's going to get worse, Dean.
你会变得更糟的
You're gonna get worse!
你还好吧
You okay?
他说"河水终结于源头"
He said, "The river ends at the source."
什么意思
What does that mean?
也许没什么
Maybe nothing.
这是在你们冲进来前他说的最后一句话
It's the last thing he said before you guys busted in.
迪恩
Dean...
听着  我们没办法
Look, man, we had to.
别说了
Hey. No.
我明白  行吗
I get it, all right?
我
I...
我本打算杀了他
I was gonna kill him.
我没法阻止自己
And I couldn't stop myself.
我们会弄明白的  好吗
We'll figure it out, all right?
记得小卡说过需要一个强大的力量吗
Remember what Cass said about needing a-a powerful force?
是的  怎么了
Yeah. So?
我一直在想  听着
So...I've been thinking. Look...
该隐仍然有血印  对吗
Cain still has the Mark, right?
他一直带着它
And he's lived with it.
多年来  他一直带着它
For years, he's lived with it.
所以  的确  血印
So, yeah, the -- the Mark is...
很强大  但是
strong, but...
迪恩  也许你有一部分
Dean, maybe there's a part of you that...
想要向它投降
wants to give into it.
也许你得与之斗争
And maybe you have to fight that, you know?
也许
Maybe...
那一部分强大的力量得是你
part of that powerful force has to be you.
嗯
Yeah.
我是克莱尔
It's Claire.
我认真想过了
I've thought it over.
也许听听你的话才公平
Maybe it's only fair to hear your side of it.
毕竟
I mean...
卡西迪奥似乎非常
Castiel seemed to trust you...
信任你
a lot.
嗯  好  你想在哪见
Yeah, okay. Where do you want to meet?
不
No!
不  不
No! No!
克莱尔
Claire.
你是怎么找到我的
How the hell did you find me?
天使能够找到向他祈祷的人
Angels are able to find those who pray to them.
祈祷
Pray?
相信我  我很久以前就放弃祈祷了
Oh, believe me, I gave up praying a long time ago.
并不非得是正式的祈祷
It doesn't have to be a formal prayer.
我能接收到  渴望
I can pick up on a -- a longing.
也许你想告诉我什么
Perhaps you wanted to tell me something.
没有
No.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许吧
Maybe.
我想我只是
I guess I just...
想要告诉你  我考虑了你说的话
wanted to tell you that I thought about what you said.
我会努力改变生活的方式
I'm gonna try doing things a little bit different,
放弃我心中的兽性
let go of the little bit of monster in me.
那么
Well, um...
我可以尽力帮你
I could -- could try to help you with that.
我还是得一个人走
I still got to go it alone.
但我可以
But I could...
也许偶尔打打电话
maybe call sometime.
你快走吧
Get out of here, would you?
有辆这么丑的车停在这里  没人会载我的
No one's gonna pick me up with that butt-ugly car sitting there.
回见了  克莱尔
I'll see you, Claire.
你可能不在乎  但是
Not that you care, but...
我喜欢你系领带
I like you better in a tie.